I see the module Good.
I'll be quick.
Thiss
Mrs Haiti's.
They think this is not the time.
It's
devil.
Open the modules casing
a lawyer Do as I say, or always lost.
T calculated
entity can destroy me.
Maybe you are.
But that's it
Destroyed.
Rough going.
But you survived.
If you knew Haiti's was there and you send me to him,
I won't deny with your life.
Look, it was the only way.
No, but the focus network down.
We can both get what we want.
Access to the secrets of $0.
I'm past trusting you with secrets.
Good.
That means you're rising up.
Trust is for fools.
It shifts crumbles like sand Poor foundation for any partnership but mutual self interest That is a solid bedrock upon which he would I might build new signs of understanding.
We both need answers.
A lowly thanks to you were on the verge of grasping.
It's in full.
We'll speak again.
You miserable.
If I could toss this focus and be rid of you.
Silence!
I would,
but we both know I need it.
What followed is
zero dark.
Quiet!
Now
you can stop tensing up.
Oh,
what
Come on.
Right on target.
Ceiling there,
you know?
Yeah.
You
okay,
E?
Okay,
you
My focus is receiving another signal, you know,
There it is.
Another turtleneck.
Calm, calm.
Okay.
I need to get up to the tall next.
Got their attention.
The storm's gonna back down before I D'oh!
They're scanning for me!
Don't make it to be
scurried away.
Way
feet!
None will stand against us.
You
passed the test.
You know
so much for being careful
Here.
I should be able to turn back to the turtleneck from here.
Me now to climb up to its head
to spoil your fun.
Here?
No,
that storm blowing in moves like water.
Sun fall!
The mad king drawn some of palace.
A bulwark of cardamom might against the howling Forbidden quest.
Thanks for the history lesson.
But they have no idea what lies beneath.
We will learn much from this alloy.
That's what I'm hoping.
Field Storey
cease fires back.
How could you just all right?
No, we're here for a reason.
I just miss feeling useful.
He's always been a wretched man.
I never would have thought both capable of this.
Buy what you need.
Leave the rest
don't pass up these goods.
Would you like to buy something today?
You won't find better.
Wears.
I got all the best here.
Take a look at these where
a proud tradition of coach.
It's not like this in Meridian, at least
in time, I'm not sure.
Now we get to see if your attack on their focus network was entirely successful.
What are you talking about?
Did I crash the network or not?
In theory, all should be, well.
Success.
Welcome to the Citadel, a lawyer.
I'll cheque back with you in a moment of need.
Time circulate
outlanders.
If you want to hear about today's bounties, head for the ruminations.
Today you're not going to make any shards by standing out here.
Filthy mercenary bottom feeders.
I'll take the shots, even if it means having a listener Bahamas waiting around for Outlander around something's air inside, he saw.
That makes me anxious.
Just fire it.
Let's be generous.
A month
by the glory of the sun revealed
behold, radiant Biederman, the one true son, King
light in shadow, whose will is light on host like is Law.
I command Lucien's behalf us to speak on my behalf
by the will of radiant Peterman.
Does the sun glare down mercilessly upon the trader?
So the hunter who brings his head to us, she'll go A bounty of 500 shards Where prisoners don't you think
not only did the rest of you and I need to cheque 100 green tent guy in China's side, but he refused to surrender when discovered, isn't fled.
And in doing so demonstrated wanton disregard for special occasions
or if it is innocent.
So come seeing
there.
Still time to save will
the way in.
I spoke of his right behind you.
You've gotta be kidding.
Not a told you didn't worry about the Castrol's.
They'll be too busy acting important to pay attention to you.
Got to see the sun ring from on high seemed well with Kessel's.
They want us to see this boy is not.
That makes quite an impression, Nora.
You have the mark of a seeker.
It's more complicated than that.
I'm an outcast like you.
Yes, I'm young.
These the shunned We'll take any job.
But hunting are hated.
Tribe that's for free.
Keep that in mind.
Why did they cast you out?
Murder you
birth
outlanders are idiots.
But perhaps they're useful Idiots.
You're not known to kick cooks.
Kill us
if any songs been written about you.
Ah, maybe How about you only laments we're the enders of songs.
Machines spared a man spark.
We stop them all.
Ah, charming warmth is for weakness.
The outlanders.
We're only here to weed out traitors.
So least I'm safe.
I tell you for a little more food.
I do whatever work these outlanders they're doing.
And Mohr
Strange.
I used to walk by the same old man every morning, but
I haven't seen
if you're gonna watch something water, this is the place to do it.
I don't like heights.
You worry, boy.
You worry.
Cease fire.
If you've got a problem with me talkto rodent, if you can stand his breath
Another man hunt.
How many men and women can one dry blues Odin, leader of Oden's marvels You've a fresh face when you're less and I or a nearer to you'll fit right In
first impressions make the sale.
Except in this snake pit they'll take whoever shows up.
This isn't your first job for the shadow Kharja scared of their own shadows card.
You're more like they spit on me, but the shards are good.
Look at those nobles.
I say noble, But you can't dress a rat in silk and call it a wrap king.
Can you
sun Fall is a house of clay.
If you were to stamp your foot, it would all crumble.
Shouldn't you will be setting out to hunt with it?
Have you never done this before?
Whoever goes first just leads the others.
Just take a load off and avail yourself of some Kharja booze until someone sniffs out a trail.
Then watch to seek out our prey straight as a ravage er shot zip.
Are you sure you're gonna be able to walk in a straight line?
What are you getting at?
Do you think did what they're accusing him of?
I hope so.
It'll make it more dangerous.
My advice.
It's best not to ever think such things, uh, overthink whether he's guilty or innocent.
You let all these thoughts in your head you'll never make it as a mercenary.
Only thing that matters is dead or alive.
If they say alive, bring a rag to stuff in its mouth with these days, no one wants alive.
Farewell.
Oh, dn't good hunting.
If I should have cause to kill you, you won't suffer.
Oh thanks
Sun and shadow.
If you can't trust Booth it, Who can you trust?
As to the ceasefire?
Is the cease fire gonna put more food on our table?
I very much doubt it.
Nice to have a break.
Work's been hardly.
I saw Castro talking.
The food is from Dowager Queen Asadi little ones.
Her Highness knows times are hard and helps when she can
eat.
But bring some home for your families if you have one.
I've heard whispers about you.
Rides, machines, fancy spear, delightful freckles.
Some even say you have a conscience.
How extraordinary!
Who are you?
You're obviously not one of the shadow Kharja.
My name is Van ASHA.
For now, all you need to know is that I'm a whisper of reason in this howling pit of insanity.
Stop being evasive and tell me who you really are.
Stop being evasive.
You might as well tell me to stop being charming.
It's impossible, but I like you.
So I'll tell you a secret.
I have friends and Meridian and I'd like to do favours for them.
when I can.
Cool said might be of use to them.
He's a good man.
So naturally the Shadow Kharja wanna murder him.
I've done some digging and I think he's headed for the green climb.
It won't take those mercenaries long to find him.
He could use some help.
If you're so inclined.
What makes you think he's on the green climb?
He knows he'll be pursued.
So he needs a hideout that's both familiar and defensible.
He won single handedly held off an entire abandoned clan in those foothills.
My guess is that it would fall back on what work before.
How do you know if it is innocent?
I'm excellent at making enquiries.
Look, he feeds orphans from his own rations and personally punishes anyone who hurts the old or infirm.
The idea that he would try to kill a demon is ridiculous.
He must have found something that could embarrass the priesthood.
Otherwise, Bahamas wouldn't risk marking such a well regarded man for death.
I'll do what I can truth it.
But what about you?
What about me?
What?
What will you do while I risk my life?
Useful things, little huntress.
Look for three dead trees south of sun fall.
They marked this thought of the green climb.
Good luck.
Cool,
Fascinating.
If they weren't looking for me,
three dead trees, just like the nausea said.
Let's see if it came from
here.
But
yeah,
alright, you made it.
Where did you go?
Food scraps.
But if it stopped to see if he's being followed, he must have kept going.
I've got to catch up.
Interview.
Doll Gord opens up about far Zenith a little February 28 2061 Osvaldo Gord never stopped smiling.
Before last month, the Danish Tech Wonder Kid was known primarily as the creator and CEO of all, seeing Dad Hollow, the world's most popular holla film sharing service.
But for the past few weeks, Dollar has been the public face of far Zenith.
The self described future is consortium responsible for reviving the Odyssey Colony ship project.
Asphalt seems an unlikely spokesman for a shadowy group of billionaires, but maybe that's the point.
He is bright eyed, handsome in a nerdy rail thin way, endlessly enthusiastic.
When I arrived at the all seeing offices for our interview, he glances behind me as if waiting for a holla camera crew to swarming in my wake.
So this will be published.
His text and article.
He speaks English with barely any accent at all.
Why not in his smile and possibly widens?
That is just incredible, really, really super quaint.
Love it, us falls countenance, maybe exuberantly inviting.
But the organisation for which he serves his mouthpiece is anything but.
To date, he is the only publicly acknowledged member of Far Xena, which claims to comprise 77 of the world's wealthiest persons.
It's more fun this way, don't you think?
Asks us fault mystery.
It's What would you call it?
It's stage craft, far Zenit.
This's much performance art as it is a functional futurist endeavour, although it's that as well.
I can tell you that there's nothing sinister about it wear devoted not only to extending humanity's legacy beyond the solar system, but also to making the world sexier, I suppose.
More interesting.
Far Zenith is science and transcendence, but it's also fashion rock and roll.
You see Well, no, I don't, but I don't tell us followed that.
Instead, I asked him a question that's been on the minds of a lot of people since far Zenith purchased the unfinished Colony ship.
If the combined efforts of the US, China, India, Japan and the Western European Alliance couldn't finish the Odyssey.
What makes far Xena think it can, he says.
Here's where I get to blow your mind.
Very exciting way.
We're not interested in escaping a dying world.
For us.
This is not an act of panic or adrenal survival reflex.
The Odyssey.
Under the stewardship of far scene, it will be a triumph, not a retreat.
This is why we will succeed.
Why we already have succeeded.
Really?
Osvald makes it hard to press for answers.
His answers are labyrinth I in but something in his tone and his body language makes them feel downright linear.
How much of this is a put on data?
Corrupted
Odyssey ready for launch imminently.
High orbit.
April 1st 2065.
We're not blind to the irony of making this announcement on April 1st said far Xena spokesman has evolved all Gordon alive hollow cast this morning.
But I can assure you this is not a prank.
Construction on the Odyssey is complete.
All systems appear to be entirely operational.
In short, we're ready to go.
All that remains is to run comprehensive system tests, especially of the bleeding edge, antimatter, pulse drives and result various minor logistical details.
The announcement comes a mere four years after far seen its purchase of the derelict Odyssey abandoned in orbit in July 2057.
Doll Gord wrapped the announcement by fielding questions from press law guns the size of the crew doll.
Gord said, adult humans very minimal 50 to 60 individuals.
But of course the living and breathing folks aren't the real head count here.
That would be the 200,000 psychos in cryo storage.
When asked about the projected launch date, Doll, Gord answered, We're absolutely going to hit this July date.
Obviously, we would have loved another few years to train our crew.
But with the situation on Earth deteriorating as it is, we've decided to move aggressively.
Asked if he has any parting words for humanity, Ostwald nod solemnly way share the hope that zero Don will reverse Earth's terrible crisis.
Either way, we have far Zenith are committed to doing all we can do to ensure that humanity has a future if not on its home planet than elsewhere.
As to the remaining 76 members of Far Zenith in their identities, Dell Gordo remained characteristically coy.
They're fine, he said.
Thanks for asking.